爸爸声音。美国人在文化上更容易信任父亲、牧师、法官等人的低沉嗓音。
The Daddy Voice Americans are culturally programmed to trust the deep voices of
在加拿大麦克马斯特大学的一项研究中，
authority. In a study from McMaster University in Canada, published in the
发表于《进化与人类行为》杂志；研究人员发现，低音高的男性声音
Journal of Evolution and Human Behavior, researchers found that men with lower-pitched
比高音高的男性声音显得更有支配力、更有吸引力。
voices are found to be more dominant and attractive than are men with
他们发现，较低音高的声音与
higher-pitched voices. They found that lower-pitched voices are associated with
比起高音高的声音，低音高的声音更常让听众联想到有利的人格特质。
favorable personality traits more often than our higher-pitched voices. Listeners
听众被要求评估说话者的吸引力、诚实度、领导潜力、
were asked to assess the attractiveness, honesty, leadership potential, and
对于几乎每一个属性来说，
intelligence, among other qualities, of the speakers. For nearly every attribute
在评分时，参与者明显更倾向于
they were asked to rate, participants were significantly more likely to prefer the
低沉的声音。想想全国广播员使用的那种深沉、悦耳的
deeper voice. Think of national broadcasters and the deep, mellifluous
音色。如果你把声音压低，会发现美国人变得更
tones they use. If you deepen your voice, you'll find that Americans become more
为了抓住这种声音，回想一下你父亲过去会用什么语气
respectful and attentive. To capture this voice, hark back to when your dad would
即使你从未有过这种经历，也可以这样想象。挺胸，深吸一口气，
call you in for dinner, even if this was never the case. Put your chest out, take a
说 hey get in here。注意身体和心理上是什么感觉。
deep breath and say hey get in here. Notice how that feels physically and
如果从“爸爸嗓音”进入英语，你心理上的负面反应可能会少一些。
mentally. If you come in through the daddy voice you'll probably have a less negative
反应；这比随机压低声音要好。有人曾说：
reaction than just by deepening your voice randomly to which we've had people say I
听起来像怪物，像黑帮分子。这不是我们要走的方向。
sound like a monster, I sound like a gangster. This is not the direction we
想让你进入的方向；我们要的是权威人物那种平静、令人安心的声音。
want to push you in but rather the calm reassuring voice of an authority figure.
肩膀向后，下巴抬起，胸部打开，从横膈膜发声，并放松你的
Shoulders back, chin up, chest out, Project from your diaphragm and relax your
喉咙。
throat.